My god.
Get Carter and get out of here.
- It's all gone.
- Doesn't matter.
We start again.
I'm sorry.
Truth be told. we don't
normally open the lairage
- for anything less than 50 head.
- Well. six
turns into 50. 50 turns into 150.
Till you get to 150. That's
how the biscuit breaks.
Are you a fucking snitch. Wes?
What are you talking about?
You fucking killed him.
You a good vet?
I believe so. yes.
Then do your job.
You're free to go.
You bailed me out?
I'm oreana.
This life here is gonna work. isn't it?
We'll make it work.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
All right.
You got it. I appreciate it.
Start packing your shit up.
Where we going?
She's hungry.
Well. I've called everyone I know.
And?
Walker told me about
an opportunity in Texas.
Texas?
Yeah.
Where in Texas?
I don't know. Some small
town called rio Paloma.
About an hour from the border.
How much land?
Five thousand acres.
black Angus. 175 head on it.
How much are they asking?
About every nickel we got.
Cheaper than rebuilding
here. that's for sure.
Will it give us the life we want. baby?
In success. yeah.
- Want to take a ride?
- I don't want
to spend another night here.
We gave this place all we got. didn't we?
Sweetheart.
Montana will always be our home.
Many people wanted to buy this place.
The Jacksons have
been after it for 20 years.
but they would've turned
it into something soulless.
I don't want this ranch
to become something I can't recognize.
We want to keep it just as it is.
The prospect of someday
feeding folks with our beef...
that was Billy's dying pride and joy.
Rip. I'm trusting that you
will fulfill that prospect.
That's all that matters to me.
Because he was all that mattered.
Yes. ma'am.
Carter. there are four horses in that barn.
Be a dear and saddle 'em.
These old bones may
move like a tired mule. but...
I would like to take one
final ride around our ranch
before it becomes yours.
Of course.
Honey. I'm gonna go help the boy saddle.
I didn't know your daddy.
Except by reputation and...
what I later read in the papers.
No one really knew him.
He was a man though.
Man. I suspect. not all
that different from Billy.
I think so.
When I think of what
you all have endured...
That fire in Dillon. it's...
They're the broken bits...
that will someday create
a beautiful mosaic for you here.
It's already beautiful. Jeanie.
I understand stewardship.
My husband and I will honor it.
Good.
Now. there's one more
thing we got to discuss.
Yeah. what's that?
His name is azul ramos.
Fifteen hundred. Two
thousand dollars... Cold beer.
Thanks. baby.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Four. now five.
Forty-five hundred. out of here.
Forty-five?
Forty-five here.
Now five thousand dollars.
That's my friend from
the slaughterhouse.
Hey.
Buyer number 223.
Fucking grizzly in Gucci.
Yeah?
Registered black Angus
bull. Weighing 1.900...
This is our boy here. honey.
Here we go.
How much here?
Four. now five.
Five thousand dollars. Ma'am?
Six thousand dollars.
Sixty-five.
Now seven. It's seven.
Now eight thousand right here.
Nine... Now ten. At ten.
Again.
At ten-five.
Ten-five-five here?
Sold to him over at ten thousand.
five hundred dollars.
Buyer 106. man in black.
Buyer 106.
Really appreciate y'all buying bullet.
You deliver? I want to
turn him out during the day.
- Happy to.
- I'll write my address down
and my phone number. You
call me when you're headed out.
Yes. sir.
Two. three days tops. I'm back.
Not this time.
It was her decision.
It's right up here. I think.
- You think?
- It's right fucking there.
Ask me. I did y'all a favor.
De nada. motherfucker.
You back there thinking
about braining me with that shovel?
That right?
Maybe that was your plan all along.
But you ain't never dug
any kind of hole in your life.
That kind of work don't suit you. does it?
And you ain't got the balls
to take that kind of swing.
We both know... I do.
What?
He was right fucking there!
You leave tomorrow.
Why is this shit yellow?
That's electrolytes.
Looks like horse piss.
Well. maybe it is.
Fuck all y'all.
Where's Rob-will?
Don't know.
Where's Wes?
Don't know that either.
Bullshit.
It's been days.
So... Who's the foreman?
Chet's lead wrangler.
Ask him.
Wes got drunk. got a hooker.
Man. I don't know.
He got Jesus.
Just pick one and shut the fuck up.
Tommy. you standing
behind me for a reason
or just to get hurt?
Chet.
Beulah wants to speak with you.
Sir?
Now.
Tommy. you're in charge.
You heard the man.
We got cattle to brand.
Come here.
Yeah. you. Come on.
Yeah?
You know how to cowboy?
I am a cowboy.
You a drunk?
Was.
Won't touch a drop again.
Good. You want to work?
Only right to tell you
- I found the lord while I was...
- I didn't ask you
about your lord. I asked
you whether you wanted
to work again.
I need to work.
Well. you good with horses?
Blessed to be part of the Texas
corrections' gentling program.
Zachariah. right?
Zachariah moss.
Well. Zachariah. only
got one question for you.
Does your god prevent
you from cowboying?
No. sir.
God loves cowboys.
You're damn right he does.
Get in the fucking truck.
Heard you were back already.
You start coming this regularly.
you might get yourself a job.
I was hoping that you might
point me in the right direction.
To where?
To a slaughterhouse.
And one that isn't
owned by beulah Jackson.
You met miss rio
Paloma herself. did you?
Briefly.
Yeah. well. like an old
whiskey. beulah's a...
She's an acquired taste.
Which is why I've been known
to direct my friends elsewhere.
Where's elsewhere?
I know a place up near
San an tone pretty well.
Well. can I get an introduction?
Reckon I ought to if I want
to get paid for this mare.
How's now?
You know. I'm not too
proud for bribery. Everett.
Or kidnapping.
Well. I...
All right.
You're driving.
But we got to make a stop along the way.
No problem.
Calm down?!
Are you fucking kidding me?!
Yeah. fuck that. Austin Lewis.
I haven't even begun to lose my shit yet.
Now you let me in to see
Wes right the fuck now!
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
I haven't seen him in a week.
I promise you. whit. he ain't here.
Joaquin will tell you the same.
Miss ayers.
Whitney.
Back to work. men.
Sit a minute?
Sit?
Okay. Come on.
Come on. honey.
All right.
Wes hasn't shown in days.
That's not him.
We hoped he got homesick.
With good reason.
He only gets homesick for
this goddamn bunkhouse.
Where do they say he is?
They don't.
They'd be only rumors if they did.
Please.
Come on. I need to know.
Maybe a woman.
But it's just rumors.
No.
Wes ain't no Saint. but
this boy changed him.
Ask Austin.
Wes loves being a daddy.
He would never walk out on us.
I don't fucking buy it.
Mind if we stop for a piss?
- Almost 100 miles of silence.
- Don't know
if you've ever been locked up.
but I can tell you a bit of silence
is the best sound I've
heard in an awful long time.
Chet. did you know
that this ranch dates back
to before the alamo fell?
Yes. ma'am.
That longhorn there
descended from our very first.
Stolen in 1836 by an
Irish catholic immigrant.
His grit built this legacy.
And I've worked very hard to protect it.
Yes. ma'am.
I want to believe
you're the man to help
me uphold that legacy.
to safeguard it. Are you?
I am.
I mean. I can.
I will.
Good.
Start by reinstating law
and order in the bunkhouse.
No more questions. no more bullshit.
I will not tolerate disappointment.
Just ask my son.
I won't let you down.
You were there.
Ma'am?
With Rob-will... That night.
Now we understand each other.
Yes. ma'am.
Good.
You may go.
It's not the ride they mind.
It's the speed.
Slow and steady.
We'll be just fine.
I'm going under 70.
Yeah. you don't strike
me as the slow Lane type.
Well. never used to be.
Yeah. And now?
All right.
- Gummy worm?
- I'm good.
Thank you.
Okay.
Seawolves?
A long way from the ocean.
Yeah. we are.
I was a naval aviator for a
helicopter attack squadron.
Mekong delta.
Don't worry. I won't ask.
Well. I don't mind if you ask.
Just not... Not that much to say.
I was young and...
looking for someone to
save. something to fight.
It was a long time ago.
I bet you got medals.
A few.
What for?
My abundant stupidity.
You should be proud of them.
Well...
You should never take that hat off.
Only at the dinner table.
You bought the Edwards ranch?
We did.
There's a cot there in that hay barn.
It ain't much. but it'll do.
Thank you. sir.
Don't get too comfortable.
We got shit to do today.
Yes. sir.
Shit. you got old.
You got tall.
Good to see you. boy.
However you did this...
thank you.
Hey.
Rip don't suffer fools.
Okay? Just be ready. be fast. be good.
You'll be just fine.
Shit. you speak Spanish. too?
South Texas. sir.
Fish or cut bait.
Well. how... How do you say "mount up"?
- Móntense.
- Well. fucking móntense.
We're gonna get those
open heifers out of black rock.
push 'em over to mistress.
We got a new bull coming in.
Let's go to work.
Yes. sir.
Carter!
Got your text.
You want to Rob a liquor store?
Got algebra.
You'll never use it.
But this?
It'll solve all kind of problems.
Come on.
All right.
Buckle up.
Ha!
Get the fuck out of my way. boy.
Don't know
who's more upset that
Wes ran off. you or his wife.
Fucking let it go.
Problem is. you won't let it go.
Stirring up trouble for all of us.
You know damn well
that Wes didn't run off.
Getting real sick of your shit today.
Hey! Knock it off!
- Shut your mouth. motherfucker.
- Or what?
Hey!
That wasn't a fucking suggestion.
It was a goddamn commandment.
You got fight. boy.
I'll give you that.
But zero fucking sense.
I guess I got to beat some into you?
Get these two tended.
If they ain't dead. I want
them on a horse in an hour.
Yes. sir.
Claudio. My friend Beth.
Thank you for seeing us. Claudio.
Everett tells me that you cut
the finest t-bone in the state.
- I do.
- Well. I got six Angus outside
with nowhere to take them.
My husband and I. we're
building a small outfit.
Quality. family-run.
Like you.
Ooh.
He's gonna be climbing the
fucking walls tonight. Everett.
Let me show you what I do.
We're a four-man operation.
but I'll stake our work
against the big boys any day.
I'm gonna need the best
cuts to hook the best buyers.
Prime grade. certified Angus.
How old are your steers?
- Around 22 months.
- Good.
We'll lead with rib eye. fillet. t-bone.
- Peak marbling.
- You know what you want.
- It's what I need.
- Charge you market rates.
all on the level.
Thank you.
- How long?
- Three weeks.
How's two?
Hey! Hey!
Yo.
Whoa.
Shh-Hey!
Jailbird. you're still a cowboy.
Hell yeah.
Feels good.
You good with it?
I can work one okay.
Fire away.
You fucking with me?
Maybe just a little.
I like that.
Your daddy teach you how to shoot?
No.
One of the other
cowboys on our old ranch.
Now. you're a mystery. Carter.
Kind of handsome. kind of not.
Parking lot hero. crack shot.
What else you hiding behind them eyes?
Look. I'm sorry I got you. mixed up
in all my drama at the rodeo.
I'm just glad to get
mixed up in something.
You know. nobody's gonna
make it easy for you. Carter.
You've got to do that yourself.
You just got to say. "fuck it."
"Fuck all of them."
Do whatever the fuck you want.
Jefa.
Rob-will's checked into rehab.
The one in sedona?
Yeah. five-star
accommodations. like you asked.
Does my father know about this?
The day-to-day
operations of our business
are not his concern.
The ranch is my dominion. not his.
Cleaning up Rob-will's
mess is proving to be difficult.
Well. in what way?
In the way it got up and
walked off the Edwards ranch.
Well. you'd better fucking find it.
This is my brother's fault. not mine.
One day he's gonna
set a fire I cannot contain.
Well. it wouldn't be a
problem if you hadn't let
that property slip through our fingers.
The Edwards never liked us.
Sold the ranch to that Montana couple.
The late governor's daughter.
We met.
She came by the slaughterhouse.
For what?
To kill and carve her cows.
or that's what she told me.
You need to find out what they know
before it gets more complicated.
Your new foreman already
put a hand in the hospital.
Austin.
How bad off is he?
Broken arm. broken ribs.
What. was he asking questions?
Wes's wife paid him a visit.
She was asking questions. too.
Well. then go do something about it
before this becomes a fucking wildfire.
I need to file a missing persons report.
Go ahead and take a seat.
No. I don't have time to take a seat.
Ma'am. just take a seat.
- Someone will be right with you.
- My husband is missing. okay?
And I got my little boy
at a friend's trailer who
starts her shift in a half hour
and I got to get back to him.
so can you please just take
- my goddamn information?
- Can I help you?
Be nice if somebody did.
I'm sheriff Wade. What
seems to be the problem?
My husband Wes ayers.
Works at the 10-petal ranch.
Disappeared from the bunkhouse.
Went to bed. didn't wake up there.
Never came home.
Would you step into my office?
Now. how long has he been gone?
Long enough to know
something's wrong.
Did anybody see him take off?
Well. no one who's talking.
I mean. they said maybe he took off.
needed some space.
And who said that?
Was that the foreman?
Ranch owner's son.
Tried saying maybe
he was off the wagon.
but it ain't fucking true.
- And you're sure about that?
- Wes doesn't need space.
He needs a paycheck and a shower.
Ma'am. I understand that.
but sometimes grown...
are you gonna help me or judge me?
Yes. Ms. Ayers. we are gonna help you.
But there is a process to this.
We will take your information
after it's been 72 hours.
It's been 72 hours.
Someone at the 10-petal
knows more than they're saying.
That's a pretty serious accusation.
Yeah. well. so is disappearing a man.
How do I know someone
won't come for me next?
It's gonna be all right.
Start the report.
We'll take care of it for you. all right?
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you.
All right. what do you need?
Spell your husband's name for me.
That's good!
Zachariah. when we
open this second gate.
I want you to clear out.
Don't got to tell me twice.
- Get this son of a bitch...
- don't fucking use that.
Dipshit.
I really don't got the time.
Go earn your keep.
It's right there.
So...
when do you think I
could see you again?
I have a boyfriend. Carter.
Happy to do that. sir.
All right.
Azul.
Thank you. sir.
Yeah. thanks.
My old man would've been
happy to see you like this.
You know. after what happened.
seemed like the whole
world turned against me.
But not Hector.
He never looked at me any different.
You know. he'd visit.
Third Sunday.
Nearly every month.
He never said it. but I knew.
Sí.
Perfect timing. Dinner's ready.
I already drank mine. Thanks.
So. Suzanne Norris says you
had quite a night at the rodeo.
I sure did.
Some steer wrestler put his
hands on my granddaughter.
How does that look?
For beulah Jackson?
Heaven forbid.
Sit down.
- I'll stand.
- Sit down!
Now!
I sent your daddy off to rehab.
So I've been told.
It's past time he addressed his demons.
Demons that you helped create.
Excuse me?
Oreana Lynn. you are right on his heels.
and I won't accept it. I won't tolerate it.
This family cannot survive
another fucked-up child.
You can't survive it.
Just like you can't survive me being
- anything other than perfect.
- You have to be perfect
if you want to take
over running this ranch.
I pray to god that I don't.
That I never turn into you.
You grow the fuck up.
Eat your dinner before it gets cold.
Yes. ma'am.
You find him?
No. No. I was just out this way. and I...
no one is just out this way.
I wanted to personally bring
you Wes's last two weeks.
and I added his next two weeks.
That's mighty decent of you.
It's the least we can do
for our 10-petal family.
Sheriff is being awfully kind. too.
Paid him a visit today.
Fuck you and your money.
You want to talk about something?
No. It's nothing.
Spit it out. Carter.
For fuck's sakes. just tell
me. What's on your mind?
Come on. man.
I-I met a girl.
Thank god.
I mean. n-no. that. that's-that's good.
I'm just not sure what to do.
Well. you don't do anything.
you don't say anything.
You just listen. That's the deal.
She says something
nice to you. you listen.
mean to you. you listen.
And if you don't know what
the fuck she's talking about.
you listen.
- Just listen?
- Yeah.
You know. years ago.
I asked John. I said.
"what's the key to a
successful relationship?"
He said. "the first day. she's right.
The second day. she's right again.
And the third day. you're fucking wrong."
Yeah.
You ever...
you ever liked a girl
that's with another guy?
Hey.
Sweetheart.
Steak's still warm.
Did I miss all the fun?
So. what are you talking about?
Just man stuff.
By that. you mean girl stuff?
We're back in business.
Good.
And I think I found a bar.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
There's someone there
waiting to meet you.
- Meet me?
- Yep.
Do you think I could come?
School night. baby.
Everett.
- This is my husband rip.
- Yeah.
Rip. this is Everett.
I'll be right back.
Carol. could you get a
beer for my husband?
- And I'll have a tito's.
- Yep. You got it.
Thank you.
Well. what do you say. Everett?
Cards on the table. rip.
I was all for putting that mare down.
Your wife felt different.
She was damn convincing.
Yeah. well. no shit. I live with her.
She don't take the word "no" very easy.
I could fill a dictionary with words
when it came to my wife.
I think I have that same dictionary.
Knowing Jeanie sold y'all that ranch.
I. I reckon we'll discover
we have more in common.
I tended more animals on
that ranch than any other.
I had a mean crush on
Jeanie in high school.
It was not reciprocated.
Yeah. I did two tours with Billy.
He was. he was better at war than me.
They built a beautiful place.
Yeah. they sure did.
All right. how about we
get mckinney up here?
All right.
Come on. sweetheart.
Yeah.
Mama's coming. sweetheart.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm